Notre Dame: Compliance Office Records
University of Notre Dame Archives
Notre Dame: Athletic Compliance Office Records
1998-2003.
ACM
University of Notre Dame. Athletic Compliance Office.
23 boxes
University of Notre Dame Archives Notre Dame, Indiana 46556
Legal Status
Private
Access to university records in any format (paper, digital, photographic, or audiovisual) is governed by state and federal laws, University of Notre Dame policy, and the University of Notre Dame Archives Access Guidelines and is subject to review under the supervision of the Head of the University Archives.
University of Notre Dame. Athletic Compliance Office.
Scope and Content
Records of Notre Dame's Athletic Compliance Office, including VHS video tapes.
University of Notre Dame.; University of Notre Dame. Athletic Compliance Office.
- Notre Dame: Athletic Compliance Office: Records - CLOSED., UACM
- Notre Dame: Athletic Compliance Office: Audio-visual Material, AACM
  - NCAA - Getting to the Next Level / The First Step: Drafting Your Team, no date; AACM 68070
  - It's Just Not Worth It [Gambling Awareness], 1998/10; AACM 68071
  - Worth the Gamble, NCAA Sports Wagering Awareness Video, 1999/08; AACM 68072
  - Don't Cross That Line [Gambling Awareness], 2000/10; AACM 68073
  - Don't Cross That Line [Mixed][Gambling Awareness], 2000/11; AACM 68074
  - Fox Digital: The Last word With Jim Rome, Excerpts From Kevin Pendergast Interview, 2000/0901; AACM 68075
  - Benny Silman, Sports Wagering Video For Men's Basketball, 2001/03; AACM 68076
  - Benny Silman, Sports Wagering Video For Men's Basketball, 2003/03; AACM 68077